[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
What did you say?!
I know you have
a speech impediment,
but I didn't know
you're also deaf.
Right, Junifer?
Don't call me by my full name
in this house!
Are you going
to marry me or not?
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[SCREAMS] Yes!
Not too loud. They might think
I'm hurting you or something.
I'll take it back
if you keep at it.
No, you can't.
[SCREAMS] Yes!
[SHERYN] No!
[BIRDS' FEATHERS FLAP AWAY]
This can't be!
Yes, it can!
Look.
[IMA] You're such a grinch.
Can't you just be happy?
[CHUCKLES] Okay, great.
I'll talk to my staff to look
for a wedding coordinator.
Oh, Attorney,
we can't do that just yet.
Because it's gonna be
a cursed wedding.
Someone from our family
just died.
[PING] Fine.
Then, I'll stay here
through our engagement.
Hmm?!
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[COUGHS]
We're going to live together?
We didn't agree on that.
How will we know each other
if we don't live together?
Okay?
But we'll sleep
in different rooms.
Ping, uh, sorry.
Could you excuse us?
[HUFFS]
Are you for real?
Have you really
loosened up to June?
I don't think this is it.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm only doing this
for Don Nato.
Okay.
[GENTLE MUSIC CONTINUES]